Okay, now let's take a look at the third model customization approach called as continued pre-training.
So process of further training a pre-trained language model to improve domain knowledge of the model.
Now let's try and understand this through an example. Let's say we build a generative application
which summarizes the physician nodes. Now when the foundation model does the summarization,
maybe sometimes it's not able to understand a particular medical talk and due to which the summarization
accuracy is not great. So for that scenario you can use continued pre-training and now let's
understand how continued pre-training works. If you remember fine-tuning was labeled data but here
you use unlabeled data which means that you just provided a raw text. So let's say here you have a
transcript from a medical journal. So let's say you have a medical journal, you go ahead and
use that to train your foundation model. So now what does unlabeled data mean? It means that you just
provided raw data and example I have given here is let's say you have a medical journal and this is
just something I made up from a medical journal. You can use that medical journal to train
your foundation model. So how does it help the foundation model? It helps improve the domain
knowledge of that foundation model through the terminology of that medical journal.
Okay now let's take a look at how this will work. So you have your proprietary unlabeled data
and as we discussed let's say medical journal which has a lot of content. So first you have
your pre-trained LLM maybe Amazon NOAA Pro from Amazon bedrock or any other model that you want
to pick from Amazon bedrock service and then in your case the use case is going to be medical
summarization or physician note summarization. Then you take your proprietary data and that's
unlabeled data and we already looked at the example let's say medical journal. So you create
a training job in the Amazon bedrock and behind the scenes as we had seen in the architecture
it creates a SageMaker job and trains this foundation model. So finally you will have the
customized LLM and then you can send the prompt to this LLM and generate a completion.
Now an example with continued pre-training you train a model with private data such as medical
journals, documents that are not publicly available for training large language models and in summary
it improves the domain knowledge of the model. So an example best for domain adaptation when
label data is limited. Okay so that's pretty much it from this lecture I'll see in the next lecture